Hi everyone in today's video. I'm going to show you how to work out the credit
statement so you can see exactly how much you've
earned
Okay, so I've logged into my profile to do this, but of course you're logged
into your profile and
Then up here on the top right corner. You're going to want to click on your
photo and it will bring a drop-down menu
We click here on credit balance
And it's going to bring you to this screen
As you can see here, there are two different things that you can click into
that save you credit statement view statement
This one shows the statement on the old site and this one shows the statement
on the new site
We already have a video of this one on the website. So now I'm going to show
you how to work out on the new site the both
Exactly the same within regards to it will still show me the same amount of
credits. It's just a different layout
So I'll show you it on the new version now
So click into here and then this brings up my credit statement
So in here, it shows me every single transaction and every single credit made
whether that be credit made from direct messaging
Whether it be from credit made buying movies
direct cam
Private gallery sales and more all of your credits are all shown in here
Okay
So to work out the credit statement
For any given day
What you need to do is is take a look at what you ended that day on how many
credits you ended that day on and
Then take a look at how many credits you started that day on and you're going
to subtract
What you started the day on from what you ended the day on and that will give
you the amount of credit you've made that day
So we are going to take a look at the 23rd of August and see how many credits I
made that day
So as I've just previously explained we want to take a look at what we ended
that day on
So as we can see this is a very last transaction on the 23rd because after that
it goes into the transactions on the 24th
So this is what we ended the 23rd on
So we're going to input that into our calculator
So 863.05 credits. I've imported that into my calculator and now we're going to
scroll down
Until we find the very last transaction on the 23rd
Just going to scroll down nice and slowly
Until we find the end of the 23rd. Okay, here we are
So as we can see here, this is a very last transaction on the 23rd
But we don't input this what we actually do is we look at the one below it
So we're going to take a look at this one. So as we can see this is the last
one and you just go the one below it
So now I have 863.05 in my calculator and I'm going to minus
426.3
Equals, okay, so that equals
436.75 credits
Now that means that's how much I've made on that day on the 23rd. That's how
many credits I've made
But we don't stop here because that's how many credits are made. So now we want
to see how that
equates two pounds and how we do that is is we minus
43.5%
because the website take a percentage we take a percentage and our payroll
company take a percentage and this all equals
43.5% which is taken from the credits and then whatever's left is what you are
paid in pounds into your bank
We do do international transfers as well
So if we are doing an international transfer, you can work out what you've made
you will see what it is in pounds
But then of course whatever currency it's going to in your bank. There will be
an international transfer
fee and also you'll have to think about the conversion rate the international
transfer fee
I just mentioned it doesn't come from us. It will come from your bank
But yeah, I just wanted to let you know about this if you are receiving
international transfers
Okay, so like I said, we are on four hundred and thirty six point seven five
credits that I made on the 23rd
And now to find out what I've made in pounds. I need to minus
43.5% so I'm just going to do that into my calculator
Okay, so that equals
And 46.76 so that means I should be paid
246 pounds 76 pence into my bank the next day
So we do daily payments
So whatever you make before midnight on any day will be paid to you the next
day directly into your bank account
That is given that you make 90 credits or more
If you don't make 90 credits, whatever you have made will just sit in your
account in your balance
I'm not on your bank account in your account here. It will sit in your balance
here and then
It will stay there until whenever you work on come again and push it over 90
credits
And then it'll be paid into your bank the day after that
We do also offer you to change from daily payments to weekly payments or
monthly payments if that works better for you
And if you are receiving an international transfer, so if your bank account is
outside of the UK
Although the payment will still be sent the next day
It might take a couple of days to arrive in your account as it's an
international transfer
There's one more thing I would like to explain about the credit statement
So just gonna have a little look through until we find where it says that there
has been a transfer
Okay, so as we can see here on the 18th
There has been a group transfer to UK bank account and they've taken out a
hundred and eighty nine point four eight credits
So this is our payroll company
Taking out credits from the account
They do this every week or so. So even though you get paid daily
Your credit still sit in your account. So even though if you look at my credit
balance when I click here, it says eight hundred and thirty six credits
It's actually even though that's what in my account
I am not due that money because I've already been paid on it. I've already been
paid on all of those credits
Because the payroll company
Transfer the credits out every week or so not every day when they pay you so
even though it still says I've got eight hundred and odd credits
Like I said, I've already been paid on that. So this is where I can get
confusing
So this is why we do have to go into the credit statement to work it out rather
than just looking at credit balance
There is something else that I'd like to show you
So we're gonna click back up here on the top right on our icon again
And then we're gonna scroll down to statistics and click on that
And in here it gives you the statistics of how much you've made on each day and
how you made that money
so you can click on whatever date you want to look from and
Until when so we're gonna look from the 11th to the 25th and press view and
This brings up what we've made on those days
And as you can see it gives you a breakdown of how much you made for your
gallery sales your movies your direct cam
phone chart direct chart SMS
sales auction total and escort
There is one thing missing on this direct messenger feature is missing
so
There's some credits not accounted for
Because it would just be easier just to look at here and say okay, so on the 23
rd
I made
417 credits, but as we've just worked out on the 23rd. I actually made
436 credits and
The reason why it's not showing the full amount is because the direct messenger
Option is not here. So there should be really a tab here
That says direct messenger and to show me how much I've made in direct
messenger
And then that would be added to the total
But it's not they haven't put that in and I am actually gonna email the site to
ask them to add it in
Because it would be much better because it would be much easier for everyone to
work out
But for the meantime, it's not so that's why this total here is not the true
total
so you don't use this page to look at how many credits you've made because I
Have actually made around 20 credits more than that because I've been doing
direct message
But it's still good to look at to see how much you've made on cam
How much you've made for your movie sales gallery and all the rest of it
And you can still get quite a rough idea of you know your total even though it
's not exactly the same
Like I said, it's about 20 less. It's still quite close
But again, you don't want to
Look at this for the true amount because it's it's not
But it's still good to look after the statistics, so I wanted to show you guys
this page as well.